Guide to the Lincoln Steffens Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III. Letters of Lincoln Steffens
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 March 18, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 March 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 March 21, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 March 25, (a.l.s., 2p.m with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 April 15, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 April 21, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 April 21, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 April 22, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 April 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To George Hughes, 1918 June 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 June 8, (a.l.s.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 August 16, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 August 30, (a.l.s.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 September 24, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 October 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 October 10, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 October 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 October 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 October 15, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 October 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 October 18, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 October 20, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 October 25, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 October 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 October 26, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To William Kent, 1918 October 27, (telegram (copy) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 October 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 October 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 October 30, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 November 1, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 November 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 November 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 November 7, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 November 8, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1918 November 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1918 November 18, (t.l.s.) (Box 68)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1918 November 24, (t.l., with typed signature) (Box 68)
    - To Daniel [Kiefer], 1918 December 20, (t.l., 1p., with typed signature) (Box 68)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1918 December 20, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1918 December 22, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 December 23, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 December 30, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Dan[iel Kiefer], 1919 January 7, (t.l. (copy), with typed signature, 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 January 9, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 January 14, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 January 20, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 January 27, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 February 13, (t.l., with typed signature, 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 February 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 February 22, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1919 March 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes and others, 1919 March 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 April 8, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 April 13, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 April 15, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 April 23, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes and others, 1919 May 13, (t.l.s.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 May 14, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 May 25, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, circa 1919 June, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 June 16, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 June 18, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 June 18, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 June 25, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 June 28, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 July 1, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dan[iel Kiefer], 1919 July 2-25, (2 t.l., 1p., copies on same sheet of paper.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 July 15, (s.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 July 23, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1919 July 23, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1919 July 26, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1919 August 2, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 August 9, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 August 10, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes and others, 1919 August 14, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1919 August 27, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dan[iel Kiefer], 1919 September 7, (t.l., copy, 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 September 14, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 September 29, (t.l., 2p., part of longer letter) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 October 8, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 October 8, (t.l.s., 4p., autograph postscripts in pencil and pen) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 October 10, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 October 15, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 October 25, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 November 4, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 November 11, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), John James Hollister, and others, 1919 November 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 November 15, (a.l.s., 1p., on verso of letter from [Issac McBride] ) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 November 19, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 November 21, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 November 23, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 December 6, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1919 December 6, (a.l., 2p., part of longer letter) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 December 10, (a.l., 4p., part of longer letter) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 10, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1919 December 15, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 16, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 19, (a.l.s., 3p., signed "Her Friend") (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 20, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 22, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1919 December 23, (t.l.s., 2p., burned) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 25, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 26, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 29, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 31, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 31, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1919 December 31, (a.l., 2p., part of longer letter) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January, (a.l.s.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 3, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 4, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), Allen H. Suggett, and others, 1920 January 4, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 6, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 January 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 January 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 January 19, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 20, (a.l.s.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 21, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 January 29, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 January 30, (t.l.s.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 February 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 February 8, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 February 10, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 February 10, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 February 14, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 February 18, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Jack Hollister, 1920 February 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 February 26, (t.l.s., 3p., autograph postscript) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 March 10, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 March 26, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 March 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 April 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 April 8, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 April 18, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 April 20, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 May 2, (t.l.s.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 May 2, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 May 8, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 May 15, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 June 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 June 20, (t.l.s.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 June 26, (t.l.s.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 June 26, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 June 27, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 July 4, (t.l., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 July 15, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1920 July 24, (t.l.s., 6p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 August 1, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes and others, 1920 August 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 August 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 August 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 August 6, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 August 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dan[iel Kiefer], 1920 August 20, (2 t.l., copies, 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 August 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1920 August 29?, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1920 September 2, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 September 5, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 September 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 September 17, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1920 September 19, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1920 October 4, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 October 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 October 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 October 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1920 October 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1920 October 17, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 October 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 October 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1920 October 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1920 October 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 October 26, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 October 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Ella Winter, 1920 October 30, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 November 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 November 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 November 8, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 November 13, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 November 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 November 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1920 November 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 November 30, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 December 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 December 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 December 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 December 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1920 December 20, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1920 December 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 69)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 January 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 January 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 January 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 January 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 January 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 January 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 February 1, (a.l.s., 4p., with two related items) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 February 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 February 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 February 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1921 March 9, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 March 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1921 March 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 March 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 March 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 March 27, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 March 31, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 April 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 April 10, (a.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 April 13, (a.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1921 May 13, (a.l.s., 3p., with four related items) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 May 17, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 May 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 May 27, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 June 11, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1921 June 21, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1921 June 21, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 June 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 June 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1921 August 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1921 August 16, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 September 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 September 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 September 27, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 October 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 October 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 October 14, (a.l.s., 7p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 October 14, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, circa 1921 October 24, (a.l.s., 2p., on related five-page letter with envelope) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 October 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1921 October 28, (a.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Will H. Hays, 1921 November 1, (t.l., 2p., draft with autograph corrections) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 November 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 November 1, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 November 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 November 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 November 12, (a.l.s., 2p., First two pages only of a longer letter) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 November 25, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 November 26, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 November 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 November 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 December 2, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1921 December 5, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1921 December 11, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 December 16, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) et al, 1921 December 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 December 23, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1921 December 30, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 January 6, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 January 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 January 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1922 February, (t.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 February 6, (t.l.s.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 February 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 7, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 17, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 March 20, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 March 21, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 27, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 March 31, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 April 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 April 6, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 May 6, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 May 16, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 May 16, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 May 20, (t.l., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1922 May 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1922 May 26, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 June 6, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)
    - To Etta "Gussie" Nobbes, 1922 June 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 70)
    - To Ella Winter, 1922 June 13, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 70)